<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>home on where I stay up late</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content in home on where I stay up late</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 22:27:58 +0300</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>CTF writeup: Grep (TryHackMe)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/ctf-thm-grep/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 22:27:58 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/ctf-thm-grep/</guid>
      <description>Link to challenge: Grep&#xA;The task SuperSecure Corp, a fast-paced startup, is currently creating a blogging platform inviting security professionals to assess its security. The challenge involves using OSINT techniques to gather information from publicly accessible sources and exploit potential vulnerabilities in the web application.&#xA;Q1: What is the API key that allows a user to register on the website? Navigating over to the website, which in my case is http://10.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CTF writeup: The Greenholt Phish (TryHackMe)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/ctf-thm-the-greenholt-phish/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 02:24:38 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/ctf-thm-the-greenholt-phish/</guid>
      <description>Link to challenge: The Greenholt Phish&#xA;The task A Sales Executive at Greenholt PLC received an email that he didn&amp;rsquo;t expect to receive from a customer. He claims that the customer never uses generic greetings such as &amp;ldquo;Good day&amp;rdquo; and didn&amp;rsquo;t expect any amount of money to be transferred to his account. The email also contains an attachment that he never requested. He forwarded the email to the SOC (Security Operations Center) department for further investigation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CTF writeup: Snapped Phish-ing Line (TryHackMe)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/ctf-thm-snapped-phishing-line/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/ctf-thm-snapped-phishing-line/</guid>
      <description>Link to challenge: Snapped Phish-ing line&#xA;The task An Ordinary Midsummer Day&amp;hellip; As an IT department personnel of SwiftSpend Financial, one of your responsibilities is to support your fellow employees with their technical concerns. While everything seemed ordinary and mundane, this gradually changed when several employees from various departments started reporting an unusual email they had received. Unfortunately, some had already submitted their credentials and could no longer log in.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
